Hi Hermes
Hi, what can I do for you?
Can you pull up my Sunday calendar,
plan my day and tell me what to
prioritize?
On it! Pulling up your Sunday plan
right now!
You've got a packed Sunday!
Your top priorities are Hostinger
video creation in the morning and
your class in the evening.
Make sure those are locked in.
And that alien -like creature is my
personal assistant.
And I have created it and I have
been using it for the last one month
on my phone in that Telegram
application.
So by the end of this video,
you will get to know how to create
an AI employee
that works for you 24x7.
And even if you give it a command,
it will work and it will do the
tasks for you autonomously.
For example, I gave a task.
Can you look at my calendar for
tomorrow and plan my day
accordingly?
And the agent will go through my
calendar and it will pull up all the
details and it will plan my day
accordingly based on my schedule.
And next I gave a command.
Can you schedule this daily?
Because every day I want my day to
be planned.
And it created an automatic cron job
that can execute daily.
And by the morning 8 o 'clock,
it will give me the summary of what
my day look like.
I will give one more task.
I want to send an email to Gautam
and I want the agent to attach a
document which is present in the
Google Drive as well.
And it just pulls the information
from the Google Drive and downloads
the file and it will send the email
directly.
And that is what this agent is
capable of.
And it can do even more.
And a small disclaimer.
This is going to be a lengthy video.
Because we are going to go every
single thing step by step.
So I recommend grab some popcorn and
watch it like a Netflix movie.
So first let's understand what a
Hermes agent is.
This Hermes agent is one of the top
open source projects from the Nous
research.
So this is a persistent agent,
not a chatbot.
We have ChatGPT or Claude.
What will you do? You will go to the
web page and you will chat there.
If you give a task, it will do that
task.
But this is completely opposite to
those things.
This is a continuous agent that will
run on your server 24x7.
And along with that, it can write
its own skill as well.
And one of the best thing is that
this agent can work with any kind of
LLM.
And that is why it has become so
popular these days.
And do you know the other best
thing?
You can communicate via this agent
using 20 plus different messaging
platforms.
Telegram, WhatsApp, Slack,
you can use any kind of messaging
platform.
And do you know the other best
thing?
It is not only just for developers.
Because with zero coding skills,
you can build your own agent.
You can build your own personal
assistant.
Let me repeat once again.
With zero coding language
experience, you can build your own
agent.
Isn't it amazing? Isn't it
interesting?
And one more thing is that you can
directly communicate with this agent
using plain English.
There is no need for you to come up
with any kind of coding.
There is no need to understand what
is happening inside.
You don't need to do any of those
things.
You can directly speak to it just
like normal English.
And it will handle all the tech for
you.
In the back end, you don't have to
do anything like code execution or
task execution.
You just need to say, I need to do
this and it will do that.
And it will work for you 24x7.
Whether you are sleeping,
sleeping or playing, this agent will
continue to run on its server 24x7.
Those are all the best things that
this agent can do.
And after that, there are five core
components to this agent.
First thing is memory.
So let's say you hired a personal
assistant.
After 2 -3 months, that personal
assistant will get to know what you
like, what you don't like, what you
do, how your meetings are,
what to do and what not to do.
He will remember every single thing.
Similarly, even for our Hermes
agent, there is something called as
memory.
It will remember all of your
details.
Your name, what you do,
where you are, what things you like,
what things you don't like,
what you do daily.
Every single thing.
It is just like your personal
assistant.
And after that, we have something
called as skills.
And by default, when you install
Hermes agent, they come with 100
plus skills installed.
To create a PDF, it has a skill.
To send emails, it has a skill.
To check the calendar, it has a
skill.
I mean, you can do a lot of stuff
and you can write your own skills as
well.
That is the best part.
And the next important thing,
which is called as soul.
So before this, I want to tell you a
small story.
So before Hermes agent,
we have one more agent,
which is called OpenClaw.
See, the difference between OpenClaw
and this is that there are two
things.
One is soul and the other is
self-improving.
I will talk about self-improving in some
time.
What is this soul?
Let me give you an example.
You hire a personal assistant.
Sometimes, a personal assistant can
be rude by default.
Maybe they can be loving.
Maybe he is professional.
So they have their persona.
Similarly, you can put your persona
for this Hermes agent.
Maybe you want your agent to talk
lovely to you.
professionally.
Maybe you want your agent to be
rude, critic.
There are so many personas that you
can build for your agent.
And if you use this agent,
this persona will also get enhanced
as well by default.
And how does it happen?
That is what we will talk about in
self-improving.
And then next we have the important
stuff, which are called cron jobs.
What are cron jobs?
Let's say you read a newspaper every
morning.
So you read a newspaper every
morning at 7 o 'clock.
Similarly, you want this agent to
execute the same job every day or at
any specific time.
So for example, when I wake up in
the morning, I want the agent to
scrape through all the news on the
internet regarding AI.
And it should give me top 5 topics
that I need to read about.
So what happens because of this?
I can keep up with the trends that
are going with the AI.
And I don't have to do any research
for this.
When I sleep, it will do all the
research.
By the time I wake up,
it will give me the summary.
Isn't it interesting?
And the next thing is self-improving.
What is self-improving?
Let's say you are using this agent
and you are doing the same things
again and again.
Let's say.
So what does this do?
It will observe that pattern and it
will create a skill for that
automatically.
And if you use it, all of
these files will get enhanced.
Memory, soul, skills,
cron jobs.
It will suggest every single thing.
So that is why it is so powerful.
And it is one of the most open
source projects right now in the
agentic space.
And the next thing is what is inside
this agent, Mr. Balaji?
That is a valid question.
So let me show you exactly how it
looks like.
Not exactly how it looks like.
I will show you how our UI looks
like.
But think about it like this.
Let's say our Hermes agent is a
source.
Inside this, we have soul.md.
So if you know about agents,
you save all the information in the
md files or markdown files.
So what does soul.md do?
It will save your personality and
tone.
And config.aml.
It will remember your mcps,
tools, skills and all of that stuff.
And.environment file.
What does this environment file do?
It will save all of your passwords,
tokens, authentication,
json, a lot of stuff.
And then we have memory.
This has user memory and normal
project memory.
And then we have skills.
I told you right?
I want everything to be brief in the
morning.
So I have morning brief and email
triage.
If I want to send some emails to a
lot of people, I can use this.
And then what are our cron jobs?
Every day, what work should I
execute at what time?
And then we have sessions as well.
So all of these things will lie
inside your Hermes agent.
And inside this, there are two
different files.
Inside memory.
One is user.md and another is memory
.md.
What does user.md do?
It will save all the details about
me.
For example, I am Balaji Chippada.
I am sending lead data.
My time zone is CEST.
What do I do?
I want everything to be concise.
I don't want any of the random
things.
And everything.
This is what I am talking about.
I will tell you what to do in bullet
points.
And then normal memory.md.
What does this do?
My projects, my environment.
It will keep updating all of these
things.
So it is like you are training your
own assistant.
You will keep using this.
That is why it is so powerful.
And then this is the best thing.
It gets better as you use it.
You will do a job.
And the agent will learn that job.
And it will save it to the memory.
And it will build skills to automate
the task.
And it will search for the past
work.
And it will repeat all of that
stuff.
It will automate the work that you
repeat.
It will automate by default for you.
You don't need to do extra work.
And why a VPS is required?
What is a VPS?
It is a virtual private server.
So let's say you have installed this
Hermes agent in your laptop.
So your laptop should always be
connected to power.
It should be connected to internet.
It should also keep running your
agent.
So your agent will work only if it
is 24x7 laptop on.
So it is very difficult.
That is why you can use a VPS.
Virtual Private Server.
It will run your agent 24x7.
No matter how your laptop is.
It will work in the cloud.
So you don't need to worry about it.
And then unreliable uptime.
When you are at home.
You can get power, wifi,
voice updates.
All of these things will happen.
But if you are in a VPS.
It has a very stable connection.
And since it is in the data center.
It will not have any of these
issues.
And after that.
By executing this agent in your
laptop.
You are using hardware of your
Battery, CPU, GPU.
All of these things will wear and
tear.
Along the time.
So to avoid that.
You can use VPS.
VPS cost is usually very less.
And then home network limits.
Static IP and access.
And since this is your personal
machine.
Giving an agent access to your
entire personal machine.
Would be little bit scary.
So usually.
In production or office.
Always use sandboxes.
What is this sandbox?
That is what VPS is.
And you can use this VPS.
To install a Hermes agent.
And if something goes wrong.
The data in VPS will get corrupted.
So your laptop is safe and secure.
That is why I recommend going via
VPS route.
Now for the actual setup.
Take a VPS server.
And how to install Hermes agent.
For that.
We are going to use a website called
Hostinger Hermes Agent.
And before we proceed.
I want to mention.
This video is made in partnership
with Hostinger.
But honestly.
Even before this collaboration.
I was already using Hostinger.
For my own work and personal use
case.
If you look at the email.
www.teamadv.com
I have been using their products.
For quite some time.
And I am happy to collaborate with
them.
And I will put the exact link to
this website in the description
below.
You can check it out.
And here you can see.
You get 69 % off on AI managed VPS
hosting.
Virtual private server.
For more power and control.
Here there are multiple plans.
KVM1, KVM2, KVM4 and KVM8.
KVM1 is very basic.
You cannot even use Hermes agent.
Properly in KVM1.
So I would say at least go with
KVM2.
You can go with KVM4.
If you have more powerful use cases.
My recommendation is.
Start with KVM2.
And if you think it is doing good.
Then upscale to KVM4.
So in KVM2 you will already get
these kind of benefits.
2 CPU cores.
8GB RAM.
80GB NVMe disk space.
And 8TB bandwidth.
So for the use case that I am going
to explain.
KVM2 is good enough.
Let's go with KVM2 plan.
And this is the payment summary
page.
Here you can choose the time period.
If you want to try it out for 1
month.
You can choose 1 month.
But it is going to be costly 12.99
per month.
My recommendation is.
You can go with 24 months.
Your monthly bill will become 7.99.
If you think this is too much time
frame.
Then go with 12 months.
Which will give you approximately
1000 rupees per month.
So my recommendation.
Go with 24 months.
And because I did this video in
collaboration with Hostinger.
I do have a coupon code.
You can use my name.
There is a coupon code which is
called Balaji.
And I will put it in the description
below as well.
And you can apply.
And you will get 10 % off guys.
And you can continue.
And you can make your payment from
this page itself.
And once you have made your payment.
You will land on this page.
You have to choose a server
location.
Usually choose the server or the
country.
Which is very close to you.
I am living in Europe.
So Germany is the one which is close
to me.
And if you are in India.
You can choose Mumbai or Malaysia.
But I would prefer choosing Mumbai.
So what I will do here.
I will choose Germany.
Because it is going to decide your
latency.
Latency means how fast the
communication will be.
And I will click on next.
And here you can choose the OS.
Earlier what we thought.
VPS is basically a server or a
machine.
That is running on the cloud.
And in that machine you have to have
some kind of OS.
And for popular OS.
Click on Ubuntu.
And click on select.
And once you select that.
You will land on this page.
Here you need to create a password.
This is the root password.
That is going to be very important
for you.
Because once you create a VPS.
This is the password.
That it is going to ask you to log
into the VPS.
So I will put my password.
So let's say.
Okay.
I would say no thanks right now.
And here you can add additional
things.
Like malware scanners.
Or auto backups.
Or I would prefer using Docker
manager.
This Docker means.
One more container inside this KVM
server.
And choose the Docker manager.
And click on next.
Once you do this.
It will start your VPS server on the
Hostinger panel.
And once you complete that process.
You will come to this page.
Which is called Hostinger hPanel.
If you want to find your VPS.
On the left side you have something.
Which is called as VPS here.
And you can come to this page.
You can see here.
KVM 2 is currently running.
You can click on manage.
And on the left side.
You can see something which is
called as Docker manager.
You can see all the details here.
But let's not worry about all those
things.
Click on Docker manager.
And here you can start with compose.
And you will say one click deploy.
So one of the best advantages of
Hostinger.
You can install your agents.
On the Docker inside a KVM server.
With a single click.
What we will do here.
We will go with Hermes.
So in Hermes we have multiple
things.
Hermes agent, Hermes web UI.
And Hermes workspace.
So I would go ahead and go with
Hermes agent.
Because this is where you get more
power.
If you are a web person.
You can go with this one as well.
Or you can choose workspace.
But for this demo I will go with
Hermes agent.
And just wanted to show you one more
thing.
There are so many different agents.
You can install open clog.
There are lot of things that you can
do with one click deploy in
Hostinger.
So let's go with Hermes.
And I will click on select.
And see here.
This is my admin username.
I will not worry about any of the
things.
This is my admin password.
Nous API key.
You don't even need this actually.
So I will just remove this API key.
Because we are not going to use any
of the tokens from Nous.
So this is our admin password.
And I will click on deploy.
I will say save.
And wait.
Once it is deployed.
You will get a terminal it is
running.
Right now it is deployed.
That's why you are seeing open and
terminal.
You can click on open. You don't
need to even go to terminal as well.
Give your username here.
If you forget your password.
You can come back to the Hostinger
page.
You can click on manage.
And below this you have something
which is called as environment.
And I can click on my admin
password.
I will change the password later on.
So don't worry about this.
And I will paste my password here
and click on sign in.
So no thanks.
On the left side we have chart.
Sessions. Models. Logs.
Cron jobs. Skills. Plugins.
MCP. Channels. Webhooks.
Pairing. Profiles. Config.
Key. System. Documentation.
So there are so many things that
this agent can do.
First we will try to set it up.
And for setting it up.
You need to use a command.
Which is called as slash setup.
So click on enter.
So let me zoom in.
If you want to go via quick setup.
Or full setup.
We will go via full setup.
If you want to navigate.
You can use up and down arrows.
And you can click on enter to choose
the option.
So I will now choose and enter.
And see here.
It is asking me to choose which
API I want to use with this.
So you can use OpenAI API.
Anthropic API.
OpenRouter API.
You can use as per your requirement.
So for now what I will do.
I will go via Claude models from
Anthropic.
So I will choose Anthropic.
Here we have 3 options.
Either if you have a Claude
subscription already.
You can use that.
Or you can use the API key as well.
And I will go via API key route.
So what I did is.
I created an API key.
Let me copy the API key.
And here I will choose the option 2.
Because I am going via API key.
And I will paste my API key.
Simple. And after that.
It is asking me to communicate with
the
Which model in that Claude.
So 4.8 is too much powerful for my
daily tasks.
So what I will do.
I will go via 4.6 which is also from
the Opus.
And what will the terminal do here.
Keep the current local.
And after that the second best thing
the
Hermes agent can do is.
You can talk to Hermes agent with
any of the
Messaging platforms guys.
Once you have done all the setup.
You don't need to come back to setup
again.
Here we have options to Telegram,
Slack,
Metrics, WhatsApp, Signal,
Email, SMS.
There are so many options.
So what we will do. We will go via
Telegram. And to select it.
I am clicking space bar and click on
enter.
What it is asking.
If you want to go via automatic or
manual.
So I will say I will go via
automatic.
Now what I will do.
I will open my camera.
I will scan this QR code.
I will click on Telegram.
And it will redirect me to the
Telegram bot.
I will open the Telegram.
And here it is asking what is the
bot name.
Let's say Hermes agent v1.
I will type version 1 and let me
create this.
And here we have created the bot.
And I can start talking to this bot.
So I clicked start.
But it will not respond to us right
away.
Because we have a bad setup.
So once it is done.
Here it says allow Telegram to use
this account.
I will say yes.
Click here.
And if anyone wants to add
additional user ID.
I don't want any additional user ID.
So I will leave it as blank.
Click enter. And user ID is asking.
I will say yes.
And that's it. So Telegram is
connected to us.
So let me show you the telegram
here.
I am connected to the web.
And you can see I have given the
option to start.
It is still not responding to us.
Because we have not completed the
setup yet.
But let's go back here.
To the Hermes agent.
And here you don't need to worry
about all of these things.
Click on enter.
And the browser is asking what to
do.
Put the same thing local browser.
And after that I don't want any of
the subscriptions.
Click on skip.
And Microsoft says free.
I will keep it as it is right now.
And I will also skip all of these
things.
I don't want any of these.
And it is asking again.
So let's do the same thing again.
And let's put the local browser.
And I don't need any subscription or
image model.
Microsoft TTS.
And let me skip all of these things.
And I think that's it guys.
Once we have completed the setup.
Now the Hermes agent is currently
live.
So if I just say hello.
Or hi.
It should respond back to us.
Okay.
There is an issue.
Error code 401. There is an error.
But we have given the correct answer
to our API.
Why would we have got an error?
I don't know why.
After a couple of minutes of doing a
debugging.
I got a solution.
Maybe it could be a bug.
You come here.
And click on keys.
And then click on anthropic.
And then look here.
When we put the API key.
It is taking 200 and taking extra
information.
There is no such information in the
API key.
That is why the API key is not
working properly.
I will click on replace.
And I will paste my exact API key.
And I will click on save.
Now we have saved the API key.
So what should we do?
Let me just restart the gateway.
So that the API will get a new load.
Okay. The session has restarted.
Now let's see if we can talk to this
agent.
Let's put hello.
Look. Hello. How can I help you
today?
So I can ask a lot of questions.
Maybe let's say.
Can you look at
the
YouTube channel
named
Balaji Chippada.
And can you summarize
what he does?
So let's see.
It should do a Google search.
But let's see.
And now it got the information.
For the first time
it did a lot of setup.
It should write code. It should
create environment.
Every single thing it did without
any
intervention.
And it gave me the on output.
Balaji Chippada YouTube channel
summary.
24.5 subscribers.
Total 106 videos. What do I do?
Content breakdown.
And what is the recent content?
Agentic road maps.
Every single thing it pulled out
from the website.
And it got me the information.
In a single command.
I didn't do anything.
That is why this is so powerful.
But one of the issue is
how can you come here and talk?
And that is why it can support
the telegram.
There are multiple things.
So let's see.
Let's say hello.
Let's see if it replies to this
agent.
See. Hi Balaji. How can I help you
today?
Actually we didn't say Balaji
and didn't do anything.
But why did it say Balaji?
Do you know the answer?
Because it already pulled it from
YouTube.
But it remembers or
it knows that I am Balaji.
And that is why it is saying hi
Balaji.
So it learns as you
progress and as you use it actually.
That is why it is so powerful.
So from here you can use
the agent from the telegram itself.
You don't have to come here
actually.
So let me zoom out a little bit.
But what is it now? It's just like a
chart
UI. So it can do a lot
of things for us using anthropic
model.
But isn't it interesting if
it can pull the details from my
calendar?
And that is what we are going to do
the next
step. Connecting our
Google services, Google Gmail or
calendar or sheets to this agent.
So this agent
can do tasks for us autonomously.
Google services to Hermes agent,
you need permission from Google
right?
So how is it done? It is done via
authentication.
So what you need to do for that
is you need to come to this website
console.cloud.google.com
and login with the account that you
want to
connect to Hermes agent.
After that you can search for
projects here.
And click on
create a project.
And click on create a project.
And click on create.
And you can select
this project.
We are selecting with
Hermes agent project 1.
Click on APIs and services.
And you need to enable
the service.
And I want this
agent to connect to Gmail.
And Gmail API.
And click on this one.
And enable.
And then same thing
you will also give
permission to calendar.
Google calendar API.
And then click on enable.
Next
we will also enable drive
so that we have some documents
on the drive and we will
say drive API.
And click on this one.
And click on enable.
If you want you can give permission.
Google sheets, Google forms,
people, a lot of stuff.
But for now let us click on email
and then calendar and then drive.
So that is the second step.
And after that you need to go
to the authentication overview.
Authentication consent screen is
there.
Click on this one.
And click on get started.
And here app name is there.
You can provide any kind of app
name.
Let us say external.
And here you provide your
email that you are using with.
And click on next. And audience
external button. And click on next.
And same in contact information.
I will provide my email.
And click on next.
And I will agree to this
usage details. And click on
continue.
And click on create. And then click
on
audience. And here click on
add users. Here give your email.
Balaji Chippada
dot 20
gmail dot com. Click on save.
And
Yep.
Now we need to create the
authentication json. Click on
overview.
And click on create authentication
client. Click on this.
And let us say authentication type
web application. And then
we will create this one.
And here you need to
copy
all of these things.
Otherwise you can download the json
directly. And I will download my
json.
And this is very important.
You need to save this very securely.
Let us go back to telegram.
Here we will say I want
to connect
to my google services
using the
json provided
here. And I will
provide the json file.
And I will pass it to
this Hermes agent.
Hermes agent will set it up for us.
We don't have to do anything.
It will automatically do it for us.
Let me look at the file and check
if it is in the relevant skill.
And it is itself writing the code.
Every single thing it is
writing.
What does it say?
Not yet authenticated.
Before we proceed
just two quick questions.
What google services do you need?
Email plus calendar. Drive
everything.
Full workspace access.
Advanced production.
Confidant web application.
For this load work desktop app.
This is not a web application.
It is a desktop app.
So what we will do?
We will go back to the
authentication client. Click on ok.
Click on clients.
Let me delete the previous one.
We don't need it basically.
And click on create client.
And here we will say
desktop app.
Click on create. And click on
download json.
Let us save this json.
So I got the new json.
So let me go back here.
And in telegram let me put that.
And I will say
here is the new
authentication json
for the workspace.
Using
desktop app.
Desktop
app.
I did this on purpose.
Because if you do any mistake
this agent will teach you what to do
correctly.
And that is why you don't
even need to know coding.
This agent will do all of this for
us.
And it will guide us what to do and
what not
to do as well.
So client save is done. Just let me
know which services you need.
And I will generate the
authorization url for you to
complete.
I want to connect
to google drive
and calendar and
email.
Let me generate the authorization
shell.
Let us see.
It will write the code.
It will execute everything inside
the terminal itself.
Need to install the dependencies.
Everything it will do it for us
guys.
And once we connect all of these
things
it will be very easy to use.
This is all first hand setup.
Dependence is already installed.
Let me generate the authentication
url.
Now it will give url.
Click this url and authenticate.
Very simple.
So here it says
if you get an access denied error go
to all of these things.
And now let us look at authorized
Hermes agent. Click on open.
And I will provide this
email.
And I will click on continue.
And I will select all of the things
that I want to give access to.
And click on continue.
And here we got an error.
This site cannot be reached.
What will I do? I will just copy
this one. And then
I will put it here. Why?
Look. Copy the entire url
from the browser's address bar.
It will look like
HTTP localhost.
I know this is an error.
I will also
copy paste the error. And I will
just put it here.
And that is exactly what
expected.
Let me change the code for the token
now.
Let me
verify everything is working.
You are all
set up. Google workspace is now
connected with
access to Gmail, Google calendar,
Google
drive, sheets, contacts,
every single
thing. Now the interesting
thing. What will I do now?
I will show you my calendar for
Sunday.
This is what my calendar
would look like. 6.30 to 8.30
There are a lot of things that are
blocked
for me to plan my day.
I will give a command to
Hermes agent.
I will say, can you
look
at my calendar
for
tomorrow
and plan my day accordingly.
I just didn't do anything guys.
I didn't do anything.
So the agent has to think about
it. It was day 20, day 20.
And it should pull the details from
the calendar.
And it should give me every single
thing.
And look quickly.
Here is your agent. It's a packed
content
creation day. 6.30 to 8.30
chest day. And then
8.30 to 10. It's a free block.
10 to 12.30 I am hosting a video.
12.30 to 13.30 I am free again.
And 13.30 to 14.30
I need to do a Sunday live.
And
14.30 to 6.30 it needs to do agent
road map videos. 6.30 to 8.30
free block. 8.30 to 12.30 I need to
edit again.
Key tips for tomorrow.
It's a long day.
Stay hydrated. And use the morning
free block. And the back to back
live. And you know command
is that it can work for me.
And maybe
let's say we will also schedule
this task. So can you
schedule this task
like
checking my
email every day
in the morning.
And can you send
me a summary
like this at
8 a.m.
daily. So let's say
I need this summary every day.
What should I do?
It needs to schedule a cron job.
So by default it will do this.
I will set up
two daily cron jobs. Morning
email summary. Checks for your email
and sends you the digest.
And daily calendar
plan. Looks at today's events and
plan
your day. Look at this.
And this is like a proper AI
assistant that is
working for me. So two cron jobs
created automatically.
I don't need to do anything.
So every day
morning 8 o 'clock it will give me
the
message on the telegram.
I don't need to
open the laptop as well.
That is the advantage of running an
agent inside a VPS.
And now let's do one more
complex task.
There is a drive. In this drive
there is a file called masterclass
2.1. What should the agent do?
It needs to send
an email attaching that file.
Check the Google Drive folder named
SQL masterclass. Inside that folder
you will
find a name. And send it
via email to
Gauthamsph1234
You don't even need
to put all of these things.
Let's remove it. I will
remove all of these things.
By default it should
do all of that. So let's see
if it does this.
And let's click on enter.
Let me search for the folder
and the file on your drive.
Now the drive is connected
automatically.
Found the folder. Let me search for
the files.
And the file is pointed out.
Masterclass 2 and how to machine
learn
and make decisions. And it
downloads and it will send
via email itself. Directly.
You don't need to open the drive or
the mail.
You don't need to do anything.
So it is asking. Send an attachment.
This is the subject. Shall I go
ahead? Maybe I want to give
some context to the body.
I will say
I will talk to the agent right now.
Maybe can you add the body like
hey Gautham, this is the
masterclass session that I have
planned for the upcoming session.
Can you
please review it and give me the
feedback?
And let's
click on enter.
Self improvement review user profile
updated. It is learning from
the discussions that we are doing on
day to day tasks.
Maybe can you add the body like hey
Gautham
this is the masterclass session that
I have
planned for the upcoming sessions.
Can you please review it
and give me the feedback?
Let me check it the other way.
But let's see. No attachment support
in the CLI. Let me send it via
It hit an issue
and that issue will also be
automatically
solved.
Email sent to
successfully Gautham and attachment.
Subject
is enough. So let's go into
our email and check if the email has
been sent.
And click on refresh.
And see
Gautham sbh1234
sql masterclass how machines learn
and make
decisions with this subject and with
the
same pdf.
Now drive opened, downloaded,
error came, debugged
and everything
email sent. Everything
autonomously. And this is the
power of running an agent 24/7 on a VPS.
And that is what I wanted to teach
you
in this video. I know
this video is very lengthy video but
these steps are very mandatory.
I hope
you enjoyed this video and if you
have
enjoyed please let me know what part
you enjoyed
and if you have any queries please
let me know
in the comment section below.
And that's all for this one.